Register of the Brutus Coste Papers, 1940-1985
Hoover Institution Archives
- ASSEMBLY OF CAPTIVE EUROPEAN NATIONS (A.C.E.N.), 1954-1965
  - Writings of Coste about the A.C.E.N.
    - Miscellany (Folder 5-16)
  - Miscellaneous materials and clippings. Includes speeches of C. Visoianu (Box 49-52.)
- PHOTOGRAPH, 1967.
  - One print depicting Brutus Coste at the Carnegie Center, New York, 1967 December 3 (Box 52.)
- INCREMENTAL MATERIALS (Box 53-85)
  This addition to the collection has not yet been described. Please let the Hoover Institution Archives know if you would like to see this material described. Contact us at hooverarchivesinfo@stanford.edu